http://www.monarkgolf.com/privacy-policy.html

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Monark Golf is committed to observing and respecting your wishes regarding the information we collect about you on our web site. By visiting www.MonarkGolf.com, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Personal Information:
Your transaction history and the information you provide to us voluntarily on our web site is stored in our customer database. Most of the stored information is required in order to fulfill your order properly. In addition to fulfilling your orders, we use the information that you provide for purposes such as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our service, and communicating with you.
Monark does not share your name or mailing address with other companies. You may also elect not to receive any future catalogs or other mailings from Monark. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. All Monark e-mails are intended to comply with federal regulations.
Any personal information you reveal to us is protected during transmission by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information and is the accepted standard industry-wide for web site security. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your user ID and password. To make any address changes or other modifications to your Monark account information, please send email to info@monarkgolf.com or call 1-877-551-4653.
E-mail Policy:
We collect the email addresses of those who voluntarily provide it those us, either via telephone, e-mail or when ordering online. We cannot obtain your email address unless you voluntarily provide it to us, or we obtain it from a service company that has confirmed your willingness to distribute it.
Monark does not sell, share or otherwise distribute your email address. We periodically produce sales flyers and literature for our customers. If you do not want to receive promotional email in the future from Monark, please let us know by sending email to info@monarkgolf.com or by calling us at (877) 551 4653. Additionally, you may opt-out of e-mail by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each e-mail.
Supplied email addresses on our customer registration form will be used for order confirmation and alerts relating to an order. If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events.
Any e-mail address supplied directly to Monark Golf with respect to online orders, catalog requests, and requests for other information will remain in the sole possession of Monark Golf.
If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know via info@monarkgolf.com or calling us at the above telephone numbers.
Cookies:
Like most e-retail web sites, we use "cookies," which are pieces of data given to your browser that allow our web site to identify you when you access our site. Cookies cannot extract any information about you that you have not already revealed voluntarily. The vast majority of internet users now appreciate cookies as a convenience feature for shopping online.
Site Traffic Data:
Our computers collect and store certain data from your visits to our web site. The information we collect from this site traffic helps us to make the site easier to navigate and to improve your shopping experience at www.MonarkGolf.com. We do not share or distribute any specific customer site traffic data to any other parties.
Security Policy:
Monark's website is secured by third-party encryption, which allows our customers to submit information online with the assurance that they are really doing business with Monark (not an impostor's "spoof " site) and that the information they send (such as credit card numbers, online forms, and financial data) is protected from interception or alteration over the Web
Our web site uses industry-standard 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt sensitive information such as your name, address, and credit card number. Encryption is a process wherein we scramble your order information so it cannot be read by anyone other than Monark Golf, even if it is wrongly intercepted en route to us. Using a security-enabled browser (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator, versions 4.06 or greater) will enable you to take advantage of our site's data encryption feature.
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Customer's credit card details are encrypted by PayPal and not accessible by Seller, i.e. Seller has no chance to see or review Buyer's card details. For internet orders Seller does not keep, nor save, nor store any Buyer's card details, payments are processed by PayPal, not by Seller.
Monark wants all of our customers to feel comfortable when they pay for merchandise or services, whether ordered by telephone, fax, or across the Internet. If you would feel more comfortable placing your order by phone, please call toll free 877 551 4653 (in the U.S.A) or 909 598 5443 (from outside the U.S.) Monday to Friday  from 8:30am to 5:00pm Pacific Standard Time, or send a fax 24/7 to our secured fax line 909 598 5444.
If you have any questions regarding any of the elements of our web Privacy Policy, please email us at info@monarkgolf.com or call our Customer Service line at (877) 551 4653.
This website is owned and operated by Monark Golf Supply Inc.
About Monark Golf
MonarkGolf.com is a full time distributor of golf club components, golf club drivers, affordable golf clubs and golf club components. Buy golf clubs online from Monark Golf having sale on golf clubs and other top golf brands. Monark Golf also provides guaranteed low prices on all top golf brands. Click here to buy discount golf clubs and golf club head covers from our online store.
Sign up Newsletter
Get the Latest Products & Specials. Sign up for newsletter today.
I am writing this note to let you know how much I appreciate your quick shipping. I receive everything that...
Gene Goins
Sign the Guest Book
View all
Monark Golf Supply Inc.
P.O. Box 1263Walnut, CA 91788-1263, U.S.A.Sales Toll Free: (877) 551 - 4653Tel.: (877)-551-4653Fax: (909) 598 - 5444Web: www.monarkgolf.com
Delivery Delays Due To Covid-19, Packages May Need More Time For Delivery Due To Limited Transportation Availability Caused by Covid-19
Driver Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Wood Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Hybrid Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Iron Component Kits
Wedge Component Kits
Putter Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Grafalloy Shafts on Sale - Huge Discounts!
MITSUBISHI GRAPHITE SHAFTS ON SALE - SAVE NOW
OEM Graphite Shafts on Sale - Save 82%!
Project-X Shafts on Sale - 91% OFF !
TaylorMade Golf on Sale - 60% OFF
Titanium Driver Heads on Sale - starting at $7.90!
Driver Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Wood Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Hybrid Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Iron Component Kits
Wedge Component Kits
Putter Kits (Head, Shaft, Grip)
Grafalloy Shafts on Sale - Huge Discounts!
MITSUBISHI GRAPHITE SHAFTS ON SALE - SAVE NOW
OEM Graphite Shafts on Sale - Save 82%!
Project-X Shafts on Sale - 91% OFF !
TaylorMade Golf on Sale - 60% OFF
Titanium Driver Heads on Sale - starting at $7.90!
